&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：那么让我们谈谈下一个抽象操作。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So let's talk then about the next abstract operation.
它叫做toString。
It's called toString.
toString抽象操作就像它听起来一样。
The toString abstract operation does what it sounds like.
标签上很有描述性。
It's very descriptive on the label.
它可以接受任何值
It takes any value and
以字符串形式为我们提供该值的表示。
gives us the representation of that value in string form.
几乎每一个你能想象的价值都至少有一些
And almost every value that you can imagine has at least some
一种字符串形式的表示。
kind of representation in string form.
顺便说一句，在括号中我注意到了实际的spec部分，因为它们
By the way in the parentheses I'm noting the actual spec sections as they
目前存在于ES2018版本中。
exist currently in the version at this moment which is ES2018.
他们对ES2019规范进行了投票，它将在今年晚些时候发布。
They voted on the ES2019 spec and it'll come out a little bit later this year.
希望这些区号中的大多数不会改变，但那些是
Hopefully most of these section numbers won't change but those are for
ES2018规格。
the ES2018 specs.
好的，toString操作。
Okay so the toString opperation.
让我来给你们展示一些事情的例子，
Boiling down a bunch of details let me just show you some examples of things and
他们最终产生的字符串表示。
what they end up producing as a string representation.
在大多数情况下，这些都是您所期望的。
And for the most part these are exactly what you'd expect.
如果您有一个NULL值，并且您最终执行了toString
If you had a null value and you ended up doing that toString
抽象操作在某种程度上，你会得到引用空。
abstract operation in some way, you'd get quote null.
未定义的，真的，假的，浮点数，甚至是零都是一样的。
Same thing with undefined, true false, floating point numbers, even the zero.
当我们看到负零时，事情变得有点奇怪，记住这一点。
Things get a little strange when we look at the negative zero, remember that.
我们已经看到了它的谎言，负零谎言的toString操作和
We already saw that it lies, the toString operation for negative zero lies and
生成报价，零。
produces a quote, zero.
所以这是一个角落的案例
So that's one of the corner cases and
稍后我们将更多地讨论角落案例。
we'll talk more about corner cases in a bit.
好的，如果我们对一个对象调用toString，记住它将调用
All right so if we call toString on an object remember it's going to invoke
带有字符串提示的toPrimitive。
the toPrimitive with the string hint.
那我们能得到什么？
So what's that going to give us?
记住，它最终会先调用toString，然后
Remember that's gonna end up calling toString first and
如果它存在，那么它将使用valueOf。
if it's present and then it's going to use valueOf.
这就是它的顺序。
That's the order that it does.
那么在某个特定的物体上会是什么样子呢？
So what's that gonna look like on some particular object?
嗯，如果它是一个数组，例如，数组有一个默认的toString，
Well, if it's an array, for example, arrays have a default toString,
它序列化数组的表示。
which serializes the representation of the array.
这是一个有点奇怪的序列化，
It's a bit of a strange serialization,
在我看来，因为他们把括号去掉了。
in my opinion, because they're leaving off the brackets.
因此，如果序列化了一个空数组，就会得到一个空字符串。
So if you serialized a empty array, you get an empty string.
我认为那是一个非常愚蠢的决定。
I think that was a really dumb decision.
我不知道他们为什么不用括号。
I don't know why they left off the brackets.
因为事实证明，有很多东西可以序列化为字符串。
Because it turns out, there's a bunch of things that can serialize to strings.
那么我怎么知道它是否是空数组呢？
So how am I supposed to know whether it was an empty array?
但无论如何，这就是它的工作原理。
But nevertheless, this is how it works.
数组上的内置toString去掉了括号。
The built-in toString on arrays leaves off the brackets.
如果我们有一个包含一些内容的数组，
If we have an array with some contents in it,
它将显示这些内容，除非它们是空的和未定义的。
it'll show those contents unless they're null and undefined.
更奇怪的是，它的toString定义。
And this is even weirder, the toString definition for this.
前几天我实际上只是在读规范，我想他们到底为什么
I actually was just reading the spec the other day and I was like why on earth they
这样做，空值和取消定义，当它们出现在数组中时，就会被忽略。
do this, nulls and undefines, when they show up in arrays just get left out.
我的意思是他们现在就在那里。
I mean they're there presently.
你可以看到那里有一个逗号。
You can see there's a comma there.
他们目前在那里的位置，但是
They're there presently in terms of position, but
它们不表示为空值和取消定义方式为空值和
they're not represented as nulls and undefines the way null and
取消定义toString何时执行。
undefine when toStrings do.
在我看来，这是一种奇怪的矛盾。
In my opinion, a bizarre inconsistency.
从本质上讲，数组到字符串的转换就像您可以在开发中使用它一样
Essentially, array to stringification is like maybe you could use it in the dev
控制台，但我永远不会在我的程序中使用这样的东西，因为所有这些
console but I would never use something like this in my program because all these
其行为的怪异角落案例。
weird corner cases of its behavior.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：关于对象呢？
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: What about on objects?
我相信你们都看过这个括号物体的东西就像，
I'm sure you've all seen the bracket object object thing which is like,
那到底是什么？
what on earth is that?
Prototype对象上的默认toString是to
The default toString on the object of prototype is to
做那个括号的事。
do that whole bracket thing.
而这个，让我在这里咆哮一小会儿，他们到底为什么
And this, let me just rant for just a micro moment here, why on earth did they
去掉数组的方括号，把方括号放在对象上？
leave off the square brackets for arrays and put the square brackets on objects?
谁来给我解释一下，到底是什么。
Somebody explain that to me, what on earth.
疯子。
Bonkers.
好的，但回到现实一会儿。
Okay but back to reality for a moment.
它做了方括号，做了一个小写的对象
It does the square brackets, it does a lower case object and
然后它把这个东西放进去，这个东西叫做字符串标签。
then it puts in this thing which is called the string tag.
事实证明，您实际上可以覆盖String标记
And it turns out you can actually override the string tag for
使用ES6符号的任何您自己的自定义对象。
any of your own custom objects using an ES6 symbol.
你可以，它叫做toString标签，你可以改变它。
You can, it's called toString tag and you can change it.
因此您可以将其从字符串中Object Thhere更改为
So you could change it from saying Object there in that string to saying
我最喜欢的号码，或者你想说的任何东西。
my favorite number, or whatever you want it to say.
这是元编程的事情，但这是可能的。
That's a meta programming thing but it is possible to do.
因此对象对于所有默认对象都有默认字符串标记。
So that Object there is the default string tag for all default objects.
然后toString方法接受该字符串标记并
And then the toString method takes that string tag and
把其他垃圾包起来。
wraps this other junk around it.
如果超越toString方法，则可以完全控制
If you over ride the toString method, you can completely control
你希望你的对象的约束看起来像什么。
what you want the stringtification of your object to look like.
在本例中，我让它旋转，只返回一个字符串X。
In this case, I'm making it turn, return just a string X.
顺便说一下，我使用了这个方法，我定义了一个toString方法，
I have used this by the way, I have defined a toString method,
但我把它定义为一种Getter
but I've defined it as a getter so
它可以在字符串标记中动态返回。
that it can be dynamically returned in the string tag.
我以这样的方式定义了它，这样，在一个对象上，
I've defined this in such a way so that, on an object,
我也不是一直都这样。
and I don't do this all the time.
但是如果我试图理解一个对象的上下文中是什么，
But if I'm trying to understand what's in the context of an object,
对象对我没有帮助。
object Object is not helpful to me.
但是您可以覆盖它，并告诉它JSON-stringify对象和
But you can override it, and tell it to JSON-stringify the object and
打印这些结果，这样更好。
print those results, and that is much nicer.
因此您可以覆盖toString，
So you can override a toString,
或字符串标记，以在开发控制台中帮助您。
or the string tag, to help you in the dev console.
但同样，这不是我通常会做的那种元编程
But again, this is not the sort of metaprogramming I would typically do
在我的程序中。
much in my programs.